the bullish engulfing the bearish
engulfing the hammer the shooting star
the evening star the harmoni the flag
all of these different types of
candlesticks exist now while some of
them might not be clear to you that's
what this video is exactly about I'm
going to review every single one of them
to the tea and give them their purpose
and why they do this pattern all of
these different lines colors shapes
patterns are all going to make sense in
this video because all of these patterns
and these shapes in the charts they're
more than just lines or colors on the
charts these are actual movements that
happen time and time again because of
other Traders and you can actually
capitalize off of them and in this video
I'm not going to only tell you how to
recognize them so you can see them in
the charts I'm going to actually tell
you like how the [__] they work and you
can use them to your advantage every
single time so with no further Ado let's
get started but wait before we get
started out of all of these patterns
that I'm going to teach you you don't
need to use every single one of them I'm
going to teach you so you know what they
are but all you have to do is Master
about five to 10 of them and that's all
you need to be successful I will be
pointing out the ones that I use every
single day to be successful and the ones
that you will not need to use I'm going
to still teach you what they are and how
they're able to be used and you can
learn from them just so you have the
peace of mind and you know what they are
so when you see them in the charts you
can identify them and not know what they
are but just know that you don't need
them to be a profitable Trader so with
that being said let's begin so first
things first what is a Candlestick
pattern to understand that charts are
made up of different types of movements
there can be a lineart chart there can
be a bar chart mostly known as the
Candlestick chart so all of these red
and blue boxes or black and white boxes
you can change your colors however you
want with lines at the top and lines at
the bottom these are called candlesticks
because you see that little line at the
top of the body of the box that's where
you're supposed to light the Candlestick
so obviously the Candlestick come out
when you take that to the charts it
looks like that on obviously the chart
so the candlesticks are called
candlesticks because they look like
candlesticks so you have to keep in mind
obviously the larger the Candlestick the
bigger the move the smaller the
Candlestick the smaller the move each
and every single piece of information
that the Candlestick is giving you is to
your advantage if the Candlestick ends
up with a big body it means something if
the Candlestick ends up with a small
body it also means something and if the
Candlestick has no body and it's just a
line and a little box that also means
something very effective so in other
words when you're identifying
candlesticks you have to understand that
every single box every single line means
something whether it's towards the favor
of your potential trade or towards it is
against it so you have to make sure that
you read it the right way and keep in
mind these candlesticks happen across
different time frames and they have the
same type of look but they have
different types of effect but we'll get
into a little bit more of that later in
the video so up to this point you
understand that it's necessary to learn
how to read exactly what each
Candlestick means so let me get into the
first example of what is known as the
long day so pretty self-explanatory it's
when a Candlestick has a long body this
long body is pretty much identifying
that this Market has a lot of momentum
it is simply showing you that that day's
momentum was very strong and that the
next day's momentum should continue with
that giving you an indication whether
you're in the trade to continue to hold
it or if you were about to get into a
trade to reconsider it because either
the momentum is going in your favor or
against it the most common colors are
green and red so for this video example
we will be using green and red
Candlestick examples and the most common
example is obviously a big green
Candlestick so that indicating that the
buyers are in the market and if there is
a big red Candlestick that means that
the sellers are in the market this big
candle stick is known as the long day
contrasting with the long day is known
as the the short day same thing as the
long day it's pretty self-explanatory if
there's not a big body or a big wick
this is pretty much called a short day
also known as choppy Market or slow
Market consolidation pretty much all the
same thing sums up what is called a
short day because the market didn't move
much which is inevitable the market some
days moves very fast some days it moves
very slow when you learn how to read
that then you can obviously capitalize
off of that and this pattern is a direct
correlation with indecision in the
market the market doesn't know if it
wants to continue strong in One
Direction or if it wants to reverse and
go to the other side so this is a strong
indication that the market is undecisive
and that it is planning its next move
next example is the BET hold line a bet
hold line is a simple long Candlestick
green for bullish and obviously red for
bearish opening its low or high and
closing near the opposite end of the
range it signifies a potential reversal
in the current Trend especially when it
occurs after a significant downtrend or
uptrend which is also known as a
rejection in the market when you have
that big wick so that means that the
Candlestick has essentially melted and
all that you see is the wick obviously
on a real Candlestick the line that you
burn on fire it pretty much melts and it
breaks off here in the market the
Candlestick actually went down but the
line stays there as a trail meaning that
this Candlestick is now done so it's
rejecting moving on now to morning Stars
so there's Morning Star and then there
is an evening star it's pretty
self-explanatory morning Stars pretty
much the day is getting started so
everything is up that is exactly what
the Morning Star is the Morning Star is
considered of three different
candlesticks it's considered of one red
Candlestick one Candlestick that stops
and then one bullish engulfing
Candlestick it's pretty much showing a
complete reversal now that the market is
going to head to the upside this this is
personally one of my favorite
candlesticks and patterns that I use
every single day when I'm interested in
buying and then next we have Evening
Star formation which is very
self-explanatory as well it's like when
the sun is going down this is a reversal
pattern that the market is now is going
to head to the downside it's the same
thing as the Morning Star but pretty
much reverse it is consisted of a red
Candlestick that approaches followed by
a small rejection then a bearish
engulfing Candlestick reversing the
market to the downside this as well is
one of my favorite entry signals to
enter the market along with my Cent
strategy and everything that I apply
with it these two are one of the most
effective and most powerful entry
signals that you can possibly ask for
obviously the time frames gave a big
factor into it but I would definitely
write these down and put a star into it
because this is what I use every single
day of my trading followed by the
shooting star the shooting star doesn't
quite look like a shooting star but if
you get a little visual with it you can
so this is a c St that appears at the
end of an uptrend or a potential end of
the of the uptrend which it consists of
a very small body and a large Wick which
is indicating to us that it has no power
to continue to the upside and it is
rejecting the upside this is indicating
to us that buyers are no longer pushing
the market and that the sellers are
stronger than the buyers this is as well
as one of my favorite entry signals
because if I am looking for a reversal
pattern confirmation I want to see that
the sellers are no longer winning and
that the sellers are now in the market
so the shooting star is my one of my top
favorite ones as well so I definitely
write it down and put a star next to
this one next we have the two crows so
this is a bearish reversal pattern
occurring in an uptrend it's with a long
green candle followed by a similar red
candle that opens with the body of its
previous candle and closes lower this
pattern indicates a shift from buyers to
sellers next we have three inside up and
down so this is actually very simple and
it is very effective we have three
inside up it is a bullish reversal
pattern that begins with a large red
Candlestick followed by a small green
within the body of the previous candle
and the third candle that closes above
the first candle high and then we have
three inside down the bearish version
that starts with a large green candle
followed by a small red candle and then
a third candle that closes below the
first candle lows next we have three
outside up and down which which is
pretty much the opposite three upside up
is a bullish pattern signifying a
reversal it starts with a pair forming a
bullish and golfing pattern followed by
a third candle closing higher and then
we have three outside down which is a
bearish reversal pattern beginning with
a pair forming a bearish engulfing
pattern followed by a third closing
lower next we have three stars in the
South a bullish reversal pattern
consisting of three small bodied red
candles each closing lower than the
previous one this pattern suggests a
gradual weakening of the bearish trend
and then to add we have three advancing
white soldiers this pattern is
characterized by three consecutive long
green candles each opening with its
previous candles bodies and closing
higher it signifies a strong bullish
Trend to continue heading in that
direction now we're going to move on to
reversal Candlestick pattern so this
next one that I'm going to explain to
you is by far my favorite and most
effective one if I can put the top three
in my strategy of reversal or
continuation patterns this next one
would be number one so I would
definitely write it down pay attention
because this is what I use every single
day in the market and it is extremely
effective and that is the famous Head
and Shoulders pattern and inverted Head
and Shoulders pattern so the head and
shoulders patterns happens at a high of
a trend where you can have obviously
what is looked like a potential Head and
Shoulders it is not confirmed Head and
Shoulders until it does not break and
retest the neckline of the actual head
and shoulders so this is consisted of
three different Peaks but not all at the
same level the first Peak is what is
called the left shoulder has the first
initial rejection where then it gives it
the momentum to create the final Peak
which is going to be considered the head
once the head has completely finished
then we create the third and final Peak
which is simp cannot break above the
highest peak which is the head and then
it breaks that neckline which is called
the final right shoulder and then you
have the neckline of The Head and
Shoulders this is by far one of my
favorite and one of my most successful
patterns that I use every single day
with my strategy and I personally try to
only take a trade that gives me this
pattern whether it is a head and
shoulders at the upside or whether it is
an inverted Head and Shoulders which it
simply consists of the same things just
simply reversed and flipped around an
inverted head and shoulder considered of
Three Peaks but at the downside so the
first left shoulder is when price
reaches a low point and then it rejects
it which it creates the first inverted
left shoulder and then it creates the
lowest point that it can create because
this is where it's going to be
considered the head and then once the
head has been created price will then
try and create a new low point but
simply can't and then that is where
prices continue and headed to the upside
because it's the reversal pattern and
it's where it creates the left head and
then the right shoulder inverted to
confirm to us that this Market is now
going to continue heading to the upside
so it is no longer bearish and now it is
bullish this is what I use every single
day in the market and these patterns
happen more times than you can actually
expect now some of them are obviously
nicer than others others are more Visual
and you can see them right off the bat
others are a little bit more complicated
and my biggest tip to you can be is the
cleaner the better don't try and force
The Head and Shoulders if it's not there
if you want to see a video strictly
about Head and Shoulders you guys can
see this video right here which explains
it into great detail next is going to be
my second favorite reversal pattern with
the candlesticks and this is actually
very effective but not as effective as
the head and shoulders if I were to
grade them I'd say The Head and
Shoulders has a 7 to 8 out of 10 effect
Effectiveness and then the next pattern
is going to have anywhere from a five to
six Effectiveness this next pattern is
going to be called the double top and
double bottom so it's actually very
simple and it's actually a lot easier to
spot than the head and shoulders it's a
little bit more advanced but the double
top and double bottom is very effective
because you can use it right away every
single day so the double top is pretty
much consisted of a market that reaches
a resistance point then the candlesticks
will have a rejection and then price
will go right back to that point and
then have another rejection this is
where the candlesticks have created two
equal points where it pretty much looks
like two cones or two triangles at a
resistance point this is what is called
a double top so where you have two
rejections at the same exact point and
the most ideal point where you want to
enter this trade is at the retest of the
neckline just as it is with the head and
shoulders this is very effective and it
actually happens more times than the
head and shoulders because the head and
shoulders is a bit more complex and it
requires a little bit more steps but
that's why it is much more effective the
double bottom and double top happen more
often but they're not as effective so be
careful when doing that and then we have
the double bottom which is pretty much
consisted of the same thing as a double
top just reversed on the downside which
is the reversal pattern so it's when
price reaches a low point and then it
has a rejection and then it comes right
back to that same point and then it
Rejects once again from the same spot
that is what is called a double bottom
and it has the same effective as the
double top but it is simply just a
reversal pattern from the downside to
head to the upside next we have the
triple top and triple bottom so what you
might be thinking well is it the same
thing as a double top and double bottom
yes it just has an extra rejection point
which is even better because this is
confirming to you that price is
struggling to break through this point
so it is giving you an extra
confirmation for you to to enter this
trade so the triple top is the same
thing as the double top but you just add
an extra rejection point in it and the
most Effectiveness is once it rejects
the neckline of the triple toop pattern
now be very selective with it because
this can look little bit like The Head
and Shoulders if the middle point in the
triple top is higher than the two other
points so be very careful with it but
this only helps your trading because it
is a stronger reversal pattern and then
obviously if we have a triple bottom is
the same thing as the triple top but it
is a reversal for the bottom so it is
consisted of three low points that they
have rejected and again if the middle
point is a little bit lower than the two
other ones then you actually have an
inverted head and shoulders and the most
effective Tria that you can take here is
actually at the retest of the neckline
so these three patterns that I have just
explained to you right now are the three
patterns that I use every single week
with my Santa strategy and they are the
ones that I recommend every single time
there are more patterns that I'm going
to explain to you in this video that I
don't use I'm just simply going to teach
them to you so you are aware of them if
you see them you know what they are but
you don't need them to be successful
just know that they are in the markets
they are there but they are not as
effective as these three that I had just
explained to you so these three
different patterns I just explained to
you write them down put a star on it add
them to your notes they're extremely
effective and they took me about four
years to master so the sooner you get it
the better you start getting results
next we have the hammer and the inverted
Hammer the hammer is pretty much a
bullish reversal Candlestick that
happens at the bottom of a downtrend
categorized by small body and a long
lower Wick which is resembling a hammer
you can pretty much grab it and hit
something with it also the reversal of a
shooting star and then you have the
inverted Hammer which is also a bullish
reversal pattern it appears as the
bottom of a downtrend and has a small
body and a long upper body Wick to add
to that we have the hanging man and the
shooting star I know we spoke about the
shooting star
which it was actually noted because it
is one of my favorite rejection pattern
as well as the hanging man which is
pretty much the opposite of it the
hanging man is a bearish reversal
pattern that appears at the top of an
uptrend and it looks like a hammer but
occurs in a different context and then a
shooting star is a bearish reversal
Candlestick at the bottom of an uptrend
with a smaller lower body and a longer
upper Wick moving on now to my I think
top two top three confirmation entry
signal is going to be the bullet bullish
and bearish engulfing Candlestick so I
would have the Morning Star as my first
one and then I would have my bullish and
bearish engulfing Candlestick as my
number two so what is the bullish and
bearish engulfing Candlestick it's
actually very simple and very
self-explanatory when something is
engulfed that means that it is bigger
than the previous it is eating the last
subject well that is exactly what is
happening here with this Candlestick the
bullish engulfing Candlestick is pretty
much eating at least a minimum of the
last two candlesticks and this can
happen at a support level or as a
continuation pattern and then the
bearish engulfing Candlestick is pretty
much when the bearish Candlestick eats
the last two confirmations now be very
selective with this type of confirmation
because it can look very similar to the
morning star and the evening star
formation it is very very very similar
and it is not anything bad if you have a
morning star or if you have a bullish
Eng golfing or if you have an evening
star or if you have a bearish Eng
golfing it's simply is only going to
make your trade better it's only going
to make you more confident taking this
trade this is simply just so when you're
taking your trades and you're writing
down your confirmations for
accountability and when you're reviewing
your trades you see if you take more of
morning star or if you take more of
bition golfing candlesticks but you
shouldn't avoid taking a trade because
you don't have one or the other again
this is there's a reason why both of
these are part of my top two on my set
and forget strategy simply because of
how effective they are I use them every
single day and I will not take a trade
if I don't have either a bullish
engulfing or a Morning Star formation or
if I don't have a bearish Eng golfing or
an evening star formation it's only
going to make your trade better and the
only reason you should identify them is
so when you're reviewing your Trad you
can identify what you take more versus
not next we have the harami Candlestick
which is obviously used as bullish and
it is used as bearish the bullish harami
is a small green Candlestick completely
contained with the body of the previous
this large red candle indicating a
potential bullish reversal and then a
bearish harami is pretty much the
opposite where a small red candle is
contained with a large green Candlestick
signifying a potential bearish reversal
next we have the piercing line and the
Dark Cloud over a piercing line is a
bullish reversal pattern at the end of a
downtrend starting with a long red
candle followed by a long green
Candlestick that opens lower but closes
above the midpoint of the first
candlestick's body then we have the Dark
Cloud over which is pretty much the
opposite it's a bearish reversal pattern
at the end of an uptrend which starts
with a long green candle followed by a
long red body that opens higher but
closes below the midpoint at its first
candlestick's body next we have tweezer
tops and tweezer bottoms so I actually
use these in my strategy but not as much
as the other ones that I have explained
but they are effective tweezer top is a
bearish reversal pattern characterized
by two or more consecutive candles with
similar highs indicating a potential
reversal from an uptrend and then the
tweezer bottom is the bullish
counterpart with two or more consecutive
candles with the similar lows suggesting
a reversal from a downtrend next we have
continuation patterns now some of these
consist of what are called trend lines I
strongly am against Trend Lin simply
because I believe they are subjective I
don't think something that somebody can
see a certain way and use a certain way
can be considered successful or
profitable because everybody looks at it
different I think something that is
successful and profitable is I give you
a system you apply and it is the same
for everybody and you use it the same
way so when it comes to some of these
patterns I personally don't like them
but I'm just going to bring awareness to
them to you so first up we have the
bullish flag which pretty much forms
during a strong upward Trend and appears
as a small downward sloping triangle
which is known as the flag following by
a step rise in price which is the flag
pole and it suggests a continuation of
the bullish Trend so you'd expect a
breakout of this to have the
continuation of it but again a little
subjective because they're trend lines
and then next we have the bearish flag
which it is the inverse forming during a
strong downwards Trend and it appears as
a small upwards sloping triangle after a
sharp decline indicating the
continuation of the bearish trend next
we have what are called penants bullish
and bearish penants obviously a bullish
pennant resembles a small symmetrical
triangle and appears during a step
upward Trend it suggests that the
bullish Trend will likely to continue
and then we have a bearish penet which
occurs in a downward Trend resembling an
upside down symmetrical triangle it
indicates the continuation of a bearish
momentum next we have rectangles which
are actually my favorite which they're
considered also consolidation breakouts
which is a bullish or a bearish
rectangle which are kind of the same a
bullish rectangle formed by two parallel
horizontal lines acting as the support
and the resistance during the bullish
Trend you want to know more about
support and resistance you guys can see
this video right here which it explains
everything to the detail of how I use
support and resistance every single day
so after this support and resistance is
identified as a bullish Trend indicating
that the upwards trend is likely to
continue after the period of
consolidation it's pretty much a break
and retest strategy to continue to the
upside and then we have a bearish
triangle which is actually the same
exact thing as the bullish one we're
just expecting a breakout of this box to
actually happen to the downside these
are my favorite type of breakouts with
these patterns because it is the most
simplest and not only the most effective
but it's actually the most legit simply
because it's just a box it is called it
box because you just get one tool and
you can see the Box visually right in
front of you not saying you don't see a
triangle in front front of you but I
don't think it's as clear as effective
as the consolidation box simply will
next we have the ascending triangle
which is categorized by a flat upper
trend line and an ascending lower trend
line it's typically bullish and suggest
a breakout upwards and then next we have
a descending triangle which features a
flat lower trend line and a descending
upper trend line the pattern is
typically bearish indicating a potential
downward breakout and then we have a
symmetrical triangle formed by a
converging upper and lower trend lines
this pattern can til either way and
suggest a breakout in the direction of
the prevailing Trend next we have the
famous rising and falling wedges I used
these at the beginning of my trading but
I found no success in it so I don't use
them but I'm here to explain to you what
they are a rising wedge is a bearish
pattern formed by a converging upward
trend line despite Rising prices the
narrowing of the pattern suggests
weakening bullish and momentum and a
potential bearish reversal and then we
have a falling wedge which is the
complete opposite which is a bullish
pattern with a converging downward trend
line and this is where price pretty much
slows down indicating a weakening in a
bearish trend and a potential bullish
reversal next we have a on neck in neck
a on neck line is a two candle bearish
pattern in a downward Trend where the
second candle opens with a gap down but
closes near the low of the previous
candle indicating a continuation of a
bearish trend then we have have the in
neckline which is similar as the on
neckline but the second candle closes
slightly in the body of the previous
candle still signaling a bearish trend
continuation then following we have a
thrusting line a bearish two candle
pattern in a downtrend the second candle
opens within the body of the first but
closes more than halfway into it
reinforcing the continuation of a
bearish trend next we have what is
called the neutral or undecisive
candlesticks which are also also known
as dois so we've actually seen dois
earlier in the video and they're
actually very effective along with a
bullish Eng golfing bearish engulfing a
Morning Star evening star and multiple
other Candlestick patterns but the dois
alone they are also extremely effective
and can be capitalized every single day
in the market now sometimes you have to
know when to be away from them because
they're just undecisive which is what
dois are and they can pretty much slow
down your trade whe whether you are in
it or whether you are looking to get
into it and they can also continue your
trade whether you are in it or looking
to get into it so DOI are very very
effective but you have to be very very
careful with them depends on what they
are telling you so let me explain first
off a standard dogee is characterized by
a very small or non-existing body
indicating a balance between the buyers
and sellers it reflects indecision in
the market now when you have this type
of Candlestick on a higher time frame
the more careful you you have to be
you're not supposed to like indecisive
markets simply because they can slow
down your trade or they can simply not
let you get into the trade because the
market is simply not moving enough I've
seen these dois these standard ones
these undecisive that they have gone for
weeks at a time weeks where the market
is is at the exact same point doesn't
move up doesn't move down it only moves
up and down enough to create the doe
it's actually very useful because by you
seeing this you're like well I don't
want to be involved in a market that is
not going to have any momentum so you
simply step back and get away from it so
this is very useful for you to learn
next we have the long lged dogee which
is similar to The Standard dogee but
with the longer Wick suggesting a
greater level of indecision and a
struggle between the Bulls and the Bears
so it is the same exact thing as the
standard one but just the Wicks are a
lot bigger which it can actually even be
more dangerous because out of nowhere
you can have a breakout to one side or a
breakout to the other side so I
personally just stay away from any of
these indecision candles because there's
no momentum in them you don't want to
entert a market that has no momentum
same way as if you were to be a surfer
you don't want to go surf out there in
the ocean if there's no waves your job
as a surfer is to go surf you want to
get on a big wave so it rides you all
the way to the shore you don't want to
just be sitting there in the ocean
waiting for a shark to come attack you
well these candlesticks if you enter a
trade when there's no volume in the
market you're just kind of getting asked
to get eaten by a shark or obviously
getting your stop loss to get hit so
kind of stay away from these
candlesticks if you're not going to use
them to have as a reversal confirmation
which we'll explain a little bit more of
that later in the video then we have the
dragonfly dogee which has a longer Wick
and no upper Wick this resembles a te it
occurs when the open is high and the
closes price are the same signaling
potential bullish reversal in the
downtrend and then we have the
gravestone dogee this is the inverse of
the dragonfly with a long upper Wick it
indicates a potential bearish reversal
in an uptrend next we have a spinning
top which is a candle with a small body
and a relatively long wick on both ends
which it signifies at the end of the day
indecision neither buyers or sellers it
could gain to the upper side or it can
gain to the down side this often happens
during periods of consolidation which is
actually very very similar to The
Standard dogee which is called spinning
top standard DOI it's kind of all the
same thing at the end of the day they
all look the same and they all mean the
same thing which is unision so don't get
confused out there and don't get sold
different types of candlesticks or
different type of strategies based off
of these candlesticks no at the end of
the day they are all the same exact
thing they are indecisive candlesticks
what are they doing they're not doing
anything so you can't build the strategy
off of nothing now yes you can use them
as a confirmation that it is having
indecision at a resistance level or at a
support level and that it is rejecting
it and then you can enter the trade then
now yes yes but you cannot confirm that
without having other pieces of a
strategy that lead you to that point you
simply can't just trade these
candlesticks alone you need to have a
strategy behind that next we have one of
my favorite continuation candlesticks
which is a marabu Candlestick now this
is actually a very powerful Candlestick
and you rarely see in the markets on the
higher time frames simply because of its
strength and how effective it is a
marabu Candlestick is consisted of one
big block that's it no Wick at the top
no Wick at the bottom meaning from the
moment the market opened it just went
all the way up and then it closed there
was no fluctuation price didn't have a
wick price the sellers couldn't you know
pull the market back nothing now this
marabu is a bullish marabu and then it
is a bearish marabu it happens to the
upside it happens to the downside it is
stronger on both sides and it is very
very key for continua your trade whether
you're already in it this gives you more
indication to hold it and then if you're
looking to get into a trade well get in
soon because the momentum is clearly
there with this Candlestick now I'm
going to stop it right here because I
can actually go for hours on all
different types of candlesticks patterns
formations reversal continuations there
is a bunch of different types of
languages when it comes to these type of
candlesticks and there's hundreds of
Traders out there that have pretty much
created these random names and given two
or three candlesticks their own name and
they've C it their own now that is the
freedom of trading and the and just
shows you the amount of opportunity that
is out there but that doesn't mean that
you have to know every single one of
them you only need to know a very
selective amount of them for you to be
successful and have Effectiveness in
trading with these patterns you don't
need to know every single one of them
simply like when you go to college you
don't have to know every single lecture
every single curriculum you kind of just
have to go through it so you can get the
degree and then you can go affect uh you
know go apply it to to your job be
effective but you don't ever really use
it you just kind of have to go through
it it's kind of the same thing here in
trading you kind of have to know about
it so you're aware of it it's in your
Niche it's going to be part of your
day-to-day but you will never use it and
the sooner you learn that the sooner you
will start making money because you will
only apply what works remember it's not
about working hard working hard is cool
at the beginning but then it's about
what is working smart and how do you
work smart well you work smart by
knowing what works and then simply just
focusing on that alone so for example if
I've already told you that the bullish
engulfing and bearish engulfing Works
stick to that if I've told you the
morning and evening star formation Works
stick to that the double top Head and
Shoulders triple top those are the most
effective Candlestick patterns that you
can see happen in the market now is
there others out there yes but are they
effective no I have tried this by myself
for years and I tried to found
Effectiveness and it simply does not
work and that is why students that use
the set s fet strategy and they follow
all of these types of patterns they make
anywhere from ,000 to $11,500 a week as
a beginner sen fet Trader if you want to
know more about what sen forget is
simply click the link in the description
below and I have a video there for you
that explains to you exactly what it
means because trading goes a lot further
than these candlesticks these
candlesticks are the simple language
that the market is giving you but now
how do you continue a conversation in
this language how do you know when to
interrupt the sentence how do you know
how to continue a sentence well that is
where the following piece of the
strategy comes in which is called set
and forget that is where it lets Traders
make anywhere from 1,000 to $1,500 a
week as a beginner Center forget Trader
so you want to know more about it click
the link in the description below there
have a video for you that's going to
explain everything and what we are about
thank you guys for watching this video
all the way to the end make sure to hit
that like And subscribe button and I'll
see you guys in the next video